(Dreams.)
(Friendship.)
(Love.)
(Money.)
(Family.)
(Youth.)
(These were all things
I once longed for.)
(Not until the cycle of rebirth
kept restarting,)
(and life and death
became familiar to me,)
(did I finally see the ugly faces)
(beneath all your masks.)
(Since the cycle of rebirth)
(is destined to be never-ending,)
(I promise you)
(I will)
(play this game with you all,)
(until we)
(suffer together,)
(with no way back.)
=Born Again=
Today, the influencer Gu Xiaotang,
(Haishan City, M Country)
and Lu Qingyuan, heir of Lu Group,
=Episode 1=
hold a grand wedding.
It is said
that in order to marry Gu Xiaotang,
Lu Qingyuan will pay
a sky-high termination fee for her
to help her leave her agency.
(Gu Xiaotang, Lu Qingyuan)
Didn't expect in this materialistic age,
someone would spend a fortune for love.
(Honey, today is our wedding day.)
(I'm so looking forward to seeing you
in your wedding dress.)
(I bought a lot of)
(your favorite roses.)
(I'll bring them all to you.)
(Honey, I've also prepared
a surprise for you.)
(See you soon.)
Happy wedding!
(Director
of Gu Xiaotang's Former Agency)
Thank you.
Director...
You wretch!
Why aren't you wearing
the sponsored wedding dress?
You had me
get the waist reduction surgery.
The sutures are there.
How can I wear it?
If you don't wear it,
I have to pay compensation.
If you don't give me the money,
I'll go ask your husband.
Don't.
I'll wear it.
Director Li, it's a bit too tight.
Just tighten it.
Seriously?
Put some strength into it.
Hold it there.
This expression is great.
The statement will be,
"Gu Xiaotang was moved to tears
in a custom wedding dress."
(It's okay.)
(Everything will be fine.)
Xiaotang.
It's not what you think.
- Don't misunderstand.
- Why?
Xiaotang, I...
She is my best friend.
Xiaotang, let me explain.
- Let go of me!
- Xiaotang, let me explain.
- Xiaotang, don't misunderstand.
- Let go!
Lu Qingyuan,
I thought that after we got married,
I'd quit my job
to take care of you and Mom.
Why are you doing this?
Why are you doing this to me?
Why?
Are you done?
I bought you.
Quit your job, honey?
I bought you to earn money for me.
If you don't earn money,
my money will be wasted.
You know that?
To wear a custom wedding dress,
you even removed your own ribs?
Look how desperately
you claw your way up,
it's truly disgusting.
Gu Xiaotang, don't forget.
If you skip the wedding,
I won't spend money
to terminate your contract.
Honey,
see you at the wedding.
Let's use the warmest applause
to welcome the most beautiful bride,
Gu Xiaotang!
Everyone,
Xiaotang is wearing our wedding dress.
- Looks great, right?
- Why filming her face?
Focus on the wedding dress. I'll do it.
This girl is so lucky
to marry into your family.
(Lu Qingyuan's Mother)
With a quickie wedding,
she can get into high society.
Gu Xiaotang is truly living the dream.
Exactly. She has a best friend
and a good husband.
I really envy her.
Before the wedding ceremony begins,
the bride, Miss Gu Xiaotang,
told me
she wrote a letter
for the two most important people
in her life.
Why isn't she reading the letter?
Yeah.
Read it out loud!
Honey.
Don't push it.
Many distinguished guests are here.
Xiaotang,
don't be nervous.
Read it.
Thank you, my husband,
Lu Qingyuan.
In the darkest time of my life,
thank you for being
a beam of light...
(A beam of light illuminating me.)
(I hope)
(we can have a baby soon)
(and start)
(a happy family.)
Thank you, Xia Na,
my best friend,
for being with me for ten years.
(You will always be)
(my most trustworthy support.)
(We)
will be best friends for life.
I'm so envious.
- Their friendship is wonderful.
- Indeed.
Gu Xiaotang is so lucky.
Xiaotang.
What's wrong?
Is it hypoglycemia again?
Since you can't hold on,
then don't force yourself.
Xiaotang!
Oh no!
- Look at her neck!
- Her neck!
Is it serious?
Xiaotang.
Ambulance! Call an ambulance!
Stay back, everyone!
- Film it!
- Call an ambulance!
(So the happiness I bet everything on)
(turned out to be just a joke.)
(Fine.)
(Countdown to Death)
Let all of this,
along with my ridiculous life,
be completely shattered at this moment.
(Countdown to Death)
(Two Hours Before the Wedding)
Is it a dream?
No.
Happy wedding!
Xiaotang, the wedding dress...
(Pain is so wonderful.)
(It can make me deeply remember
the evil deeds of each of you.)
(This time,)
(I will return all of them)
(to you bit by bit.)
(Welcome back,)
(Gu Xiaotang.)
Don't move.
This pose is perfect.
- Xiaotang, what are you doing?
- I said don't move.
- Give me the camera.
- Xiaotang!
What are we filming, you say?
Isn't that the groom?
Gu Xiaotang, are you nuts?
Lu Qingyuan.
Tell me,
if photos of you
and my best friend get out,
how many days will the Lu Group's
stock price plummet?
You're crazy.
And you,
can you even keep
your few endorsements?
Give me the termination fee now.
Otherwise,
this might be leaked.
No way.
What?
With so many people here,
do you want to snatch it?
Fine. I'll transfer it
to you right away.
Are you happy now?
Not really.
You like to act, don't you?
Then join me for another act.
But this time,
I'll be the lead.
The wedding is about to start.
- The bride is coming!
What's going on?
Why is she coming in like this?
What is she doing?
Is she the bride?
(Since heaven has given me
another chance,)
(I'll play with you properly.)
Move!
Miss Gu, you said you'd read a letter
before cutting the cake.
Pass.
Cut the cake now.
Honey,
Xia Na.
Come on.
Xia Na,
don't you love cakes the most?
Next time, don't sneak a bite.
Eat it openly.
I can do it myself, honey.
Honey, didn't we agree?
This time,
I'm the lead.
Gu Xiaotang, are you crazy?
Don't touch me!
- Get her!
- Son,
are you okay?
- Don't film!
Go away!
- What's there to film?
- Go away!
(Countdown to Death)
- All of you, go away!
- Son!
What's going on?
How did I...
How did I get an allergic reaction?
The cake.
Peanut?
How can there be peanuts in the cake?
Look, everyone.
What's wrong with the bride?
Gu Xiaotang.
Stay put in the next loop.
I'll come to you.
♪The face deep in the heart♪
♪Suddenly clear and hazy♪
♪Across time and space, eyes meet again♪
♪Deeply trapped in the vortex♪
♪Searching for familiar outlines♪
♪Persistently guarding,
endlessly cycling♪
♪Even for just a second♪
♪If raindrops flow backward
into the sky♪
♪And sunlight reverses♪
♪As the sun rises and sets,
we reunite with yesterday♪
♪I'll build a dream with you♪
♪Upon the ruins, spring breeze arrives♪
♪Even if there's no end,
I won't regret the start♪
♪Eternity like a day, rushing to you♪
♪You don't need to recognize my eyes♪
♪Following the tracks
of the days that were♪
♪A day like a lifetime, rushing to you♪
♪You don't need to remember my name♪
♪I'll be the dawn you haven't seen♪